<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help_overview">
Scripture Now is an application designed to help with the memorization of passages from the most important book in history: The Holy Bible. The heart behind the app and the main focus of what I am trying to achieve with it is threefold: to easily make Scripture Memory a daily part of your life, to help you find the most important verses in the Bible to memorize, and to create the best user experience by pouring my entire heart and sole into the development and design of the app, because our Father deserves nothing less than the absolute best.\n\n

Unlike every other Scripture memory system on the market right, Scripture Now takes a different approach to Scripture memory. Other apps include many great tools and games to make memorization very active, and while these methods are great for many people, they all require the you to keep going back of your own accord to memorize Scripture. Unless you consistently open the app devote all your focus to memorization with the help of the app, you won\'t make much progress, so Scripture Now was built with a much more passive approach in mind. I was inspired when I saw the various creative ways that my friends would use to memorize Scripture; they would write the verse they want to learn on their hand, on their notebooks and planners, their bathroom mirror, all places that they know they at several times every day. So every time they look at these places with their verses written on them, they would be reminded of the verse and could take but a moment to read it, and over time just seeing the verse frequently would commit it to memory. So I sought to emulate this exact method in Scripture Now with the place you probably look at more frequently than anything else on your phone: the notification drawer.\n\n

On the other side of the coin, how can you possibly begin to memorize verses if you don\'t know where to look to find verses. The Bible is huge, with hundreds, maybe thousands, of verses on nearly every topic imaginable, so how can you find that one verse that speaks to you amongst all the others. So Scripture Memory doesn\'t just help you memorize verses, but also to find new ones, with several tools to make finding and adding new verses easy and immensely helpful.\n\n

And this may sound harsh and critical, but I have seen far too many Christian apps that were just created "to work." Now this is far from the norm, any a good majority of Christian apps are wonderful, well-designed apps. But for some, the interface isn\'t visually appealing, they are difficult to navigate and use, their features are deprecated because they were released and were never looked at again and so do not reflect the current state of the Android system. I believe that if God has given you a gift, you should not only use it for His glory, but you should pour your entire heart, soul, mind, and strength into the exercise of this gift, so that people don\'t just see that you can do something, they see that you can do it supernaturally well, because it is a supernatural gift. And this has been a major driving factor for this app from the first day I started developing it, and I\'ll be honest, the early versions of Scripture Now were frankly terrible. I didn\'t know how to develop for Android well, I simply wanted to get the features I wanted in an app and get it looking good, but I didn\'t know Android well enough to do it well. But over time, I have vastly improved my skills, and God has vastly improved my love for application development, and I now hold myself to the highest standards in development, such that Scripture Now isn\'t just a useful tool, but one that is an absolute delight to look at and interact with. And I hope that my work on Scripture Now inspires other developers to begin work on their own Christ-centered applications, and to put everything they have in their development as a form of worship that others may use their application and be brought to worship.\n\n

Okay, rant over. I sincerely hope that this app is a useful tool to you, and helps you draw nearer to the Father by learning more intimately what He has to say in His Word. If you want to get in touch, you can find links in the \'Help\' page to email me, and I will respond as quickly as I can. God bless!
    </string>
    <string name="help_adding_verses">
There are several ways to add new verses to Scripture Now, all of which are simple yet robust. The first is to simply add verses directly via the \'Input Verse\' card in the Dashboard. By hitting the icon on the toolbar, you will see a new card with fields to input the reference and the verse text. The reference refers to a passage in the Bible, such as "John 3:16", and the verse text is the actual verse you are trying to memorize. The reference should be formatted well, but is not so rigid that it becomes difficult to write the correct reference: for example, "Jn 3 : 16" will also be a valid reference, and it will be automatically formatted to look nice throughout the app. You can then choose to type the text yourself (for example, if you do not have access to the internet to download the text, or if your preferred translation is not available within the app), or else an icon will appear that can be pressed to try and download the text. If the verse is formatted well and exists in the Bible, it\'s text will be downloaded and added to the second text field. Then, you must hit \'Add Verse\' to add the verse to your list, which will default to the \'Current - None\' memorization state.\n\n

There is also a Verse of the Day card that exists in several areas of the app: there is a card on the Dashboard, you can be notified each day of the new Verse, or you can place a widget on your homescreen to display the Verse of the Day. This verse is automatically downloaded each day in the translation set in the Settings, and is cached so it is downloaded once and can be viewed offline for the rest of the day. By tapping on the card or hitting the button on the notification, you can save this verse to your list, which also goes to your \'Current - None\' list and is given the tag "VOTD".\n\n

A new addition in V3.0 is the Discover screen, which is a direct client of the Topical Bible Search available from OpenBible.info. From here you can enter a word or phrase that you want to view Bible verses about. The website describes is as: "This Bible is a mashup of the Yahoo! and ESV Bible web services. It searches the Internet for the topics that interest people, many of which you\'d never find in a traditional topical Bible. Then it shows relevant verses...Please note that I didn\'t come up with the list of topics or suggest the verses; people\'s actual behavior has shaped them. I moderate some of the more offensive topics, however...Always check the context of a verse. The context of a verse may put a very different slant on what the verse seems to say. The Bible isn\'t a magic 8-ball or a fortune cookie, so don\'t treat it like one, OK?". To use it, you can enter a phrase hit the button to see if anything comes up, or begin typing to download a show a list of verses that start with what is already typed out and is certain to have some verses associated with it. From here you can select a verse to add it, or hit the icon to select multiple verses to add at once. The number in the icon refers to a count of how many people agree that that particular verse is a good match for the given search topic.\n\n

Another new addition to V3.0 is the ability to add packs of verses all at once, by going to "Import" in the settings menu. These packs of verses have been prayerfully hand-selected, and are a great place to start memorizing. These packs reflect an XML file in the \'/scripturememory\' directory on your device\'s sdcard, and if you put a file in here that matches the format in the file, it will also show up in the app and can be added just like the rest. In addition, when you export groups of verses from one of your lists, a new file is created and added to this directory, and can be added later. This makes it useful for archiving verses that you don\'t want to lose, but don\'t necessarily want in the app right now. There is also the potential for other Bible applications to create files in their own formats, designed to send to other apps, but I want to see a universal way to share verses between apps on Android, so I will try to search the phone\'s public sdcard folders for verse packs that can be transformed into the XML file format used by Scripture Now, which I would like to eventually see other verses be able to use as well. Hitting the eye-shaped icon will search for known formats: it currently only supports files exported from RememberMe, but if you happen to find another app that exports verses in a similar way, contact me so I can begin to change their files to this format as well.
    </string>

    <string name="help_state_and_tags">
In previous versions of Scripture Now, verses could be categorized in only two ways: either the verse was memorized, or you are currently trying to memorize it. Only "Current" verses could be added to the notification, and all verses had to be in one of those two lists. Well, I found this difficult to manage with more than a few dozen verses, and many verses seemed to get lost amongst all the others. So I replaced the "current/memorized" system with one that is much more robust (and will be much more useful in a future update), and added a tagging system, so that you can also group verses by topic.\n\n

Verses can now be saved in one of five states, which reflect how strongly you have memorized the verse. Like before, a verse can be listed as "memorized", but the restriction of these verses in the notification has been lifted. But the "Current" category has been expanded to include four separate states: None, meaning you don\'t know any of it; Some, meaning you know a few words or maybe the gist of the verse, but that\'s it; Most, meaning that you know most of the words, can probably recite the verse with only a few mistakes, but you still need a bit of work on it; and All, meaning you feel confident that you know the entire verse, but you don\'t want to say it is fully memorized yet. You can choose to view all the verses in one of these states, or you can view all the "Current" ones (meaning all except for those listed as "Memorized"), or just every verse that you have added to the app. All verses exist in exactly one state at any given time.\n\n

In addition to these verse states, which are expected to change throughout the lifetime of a verse, verses can be organized by tags. These tags indicate a particular topic that fits this verse, and an arbitrary number of tags can be added every verse, including none at all. Some tags are created by default when adding verses, such as "VOTD" for the Verse of the Day, whatever you searched for in the Discover screen, or whatever is listed with the verse when importing it. But you can also add tags to verses by a hashtag when adding directly in the Dashboard Input Verse card, or by selecting the button when viewing the verse, or to groups of verses in one of your lists. There is no restriction of what can be in a tag, how many can go on a verse, or how many verses can have a given tag. When selecting a list to view, only tags that have verses associated with the tag will be displayed, and empty tags will be removed from the database completely. The colors for the tags are chosen randomly the first time they are created, with the result that each tag generally has a very unique color, but if the tag is removed and re-added will have a different color.
    </string>
</resources>