<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">
    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="22sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="How To Add New Verses?"/>
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="Verses can be added to Scripture Now in multiple places, each with their own specific purpose. You can add a single verse from the Input Verse card on the Dashboard screen, you can search for a specific topic in the Discover screen, or you can import hand-selected groups of verses from the Import screen within the application settings." />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="22sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="Input Verse card" />
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="The Input Verse card on the Dashboard screen is the primary way to add verses to the app. From here, you can enter the reference to a verse, its text, and add it to the app's database of verses. But there is a lot of hidden functionality in this card that is important to know. The card will automatically parse the text in the &quot;Reference&quot; field and ensure that the you have entered a valid reference. The verse cannot be added to the database unless it is formatted well, but the parser tries to be as forgiving as possible, and reformats the text to be well-formatted throughout the rest of the app. For example, the following references are all valid and illustrate the ways you can enter a reference: \n\n\tJohn 3:16\n\tJn 3 : 16 - 18\n\tJohn 3:16-18, 20-22, 25\n\nWhen you have entered the reference, you can choose to either download the verse text in the versions selected by hitting the search icon, or you can enter your own text. You can also add hashtags to the verse text to automatically add tags to the verse." />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="22sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="Importing Verse Packs"/>
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="From the Settings screen, you can hit &quot;Import&quot; to go to the Import screen. This is a list of files in the /scripturememory folder on the sdcard which are formatted to be able to be imported. Files listed here are typically one of three forms: included with the app, created by the app, or added externally. " />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="18sp"
            android:textStyle="bold|italic"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="32dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="16dp"
            android:text="Included with App" />
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="32dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="16dp"
            android:text="Most of the files that are included with the app were created by Chris Cerrito, but a few were made by the developer. These lists are displayed as &quot;Included with App&quot;, and are lists of verses that have been prayerfully hand-selected to be a great resource and a great place to begin memorizing verses. These verse packs have each been tested to ensure that they import correctly." />


        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="18sp"
            android:textStyle="bold|italic"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="32dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="16dp"
            android:text="Created by app" />
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="32dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="16dp"
            android:text="From the list screen, you can multiselect groups of verses and export them to file. Those files are added to the same directory and are listed with the rest of the files, and are tagged as &quot;From external source&quot; because I cannot ensure the integrity of any file that was not explicitly packaged with the app. However, because they are created by the app, there should never be any issue with these files.\n\nThere is also an option to search your phone for files created by other apps. The &quot;eye&quot; button in the Import screen will find these files and translate them to the format that is used by Scripture Now. This feature currently only works with files created by RememberMe, but if I find other apps that create their own files of exported verses, I will try to add these as well. In addition, if you find an app that exports verses that is not supported, send me an email and I will try to add it. " />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="18sp"
            android:textStyle="bold|italic"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="32dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="16dp"
            android:text="Added Externally" />
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="32dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="16dp"
            android:text="If your phone came with a file browser, or if you have added an app from the Google Play Store that enables you to browse files on your sdcard, then you have the option of adding verse packs from fully external sources. By adding files to the /scripturememory directory on the sd card, you can open and import those files within Scripture Now. The exact location may change between android devices, the Import screen has a button to show the full file path. Now you may create an XML file on your computer which matches the format of those in the directory, or you may have a friend email you one of their files which can be added to the directory. You can share files by choosing &quot;Share&quot; when you click on a file in the Import screen. However, these files are not guaranteed to work, and if they are not formatted correctly will not show in the list." />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="22sp"
            android:textStyle="bold"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="Discover Screen"/>
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="OpenBible.info is a great website that has numerous tools for everything and anything related to the Bible and technology. One of these tools is a Topical Bible search engine, which differs from most topical Bibles in that its data is curated from the Internet, and so the verses it finds on any topic is not static. It changes over time with how people rate the relevance of a verse for a given topic. It is also licensed under the Created Commons license, so anyone can change it and use it how they wish.\n\nYou use this screen by entering a word or phrase you want to find Bible verses about and hitting the search button. In addition, as you type, the app downloads suggestions from the website and lists them as suggestions in the text field. After a moment, you will be given a list of verses about that topic. The number in the icon shows how many people have confirmed that this verse is a good match for this topic, so a higher number is better. You can click any verse to add it to your list, or you can select the icon to select multiple verses and add them all at once. All verses added in this way will be given a tag of whatever you entered into the text field.\n\nThere is one thing to note with this Topical Bible, and I quote directly from the website:" />
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="16dp"
            android:text="This Bible is a mashup of the Yahoo! and ESV Bible web services. It searches the Internet for the topics that interest people, many of which you’d never find in a traditional topical Bible. Then it shows relevant verses.\n\nVote for or suggest verses that you think are especially relevant for a topic. Help improve it.Searching for a word will automatically add it.\n\nPlease note that I didn’t come up with the list of topics or suggest the verses; people’s actual behavior has shaped them. I moderate some of the more offensive topics, however.\n\nAlways check the context of a verse; that’s why the links are there. The context of a verse might put a very different slant on what the verse seems to say. The Bible isn’t a Magic 8-Ball or a fortune cookie, so don’t treat it like one, OK?" />
    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>