<verses name="Initial Scripture Memory Notifications Verses" >
    <passage>
        <R>Joshua 1:8</R>
        <Q>ESV</Q>
        <T>
            <item>Scripture Memory</item>
        </T>
        <P>This book of the law shall not depart from your mouth, but you shall meditate on it day and night, so that you may be careful to do according to all that is written in it. For then you will make your way prosperous, and then you will have good success.</P>
    </passage>
    <passage>
        <R>1 Peter 3:15</R>
        <Q>ESV</Q>
        <T>
            <item>Scripture Memory</item>
        </T>
        <P>But in your hearts honor Christ the Lord as holy, always being prepared to make a defense to anyone who asks you for a reason for the hope that is in you.</P>
    </passage>
    <passage>
        <R>Romans 3:23-24</R>
        <Q>ESV</Q>
        <T>
            <item>Scripture Memory</item>
        </T>
        <P>For all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God, and are justified by his grace as a gift, through the redemption that is in Christ Jesus.</P>
    </passage>
    <passage>
        <R>Romans 5:8</R>
        <Q>ESV</Q>
        <T>
            <item>Scripture Memory</item>
        </T>
        <P>But God shows his love for us in that while we were still sinners, Christ died for us.</P>
    </passage>
    <passage>
        <R>Ephesians 2:8-9</R>
        <Q>ESV</Q>
        <T>
            <item>Scripture Memory</item>
        </T>
        <P> For by grace you have been saved through faith. And this is not your own doing; it is the gift of God, not a result of works, so that no one may boast.</P>
    </passage>
    <passage>
        <R>2 Timothy 3:16-17</R>
        <Q>ESV</Q>
        <T>
            <item>Scripture Memory</item>
        </T>
        <P>All Scripture is breathed out by God and profitable for teaching, for reproof, for correction, and for training in righteousness, that the man of God may be complete, equipped for every good work.</P>
    </passage>
    <passage>
        <R>1 John 2:3-6</R>
        <Q>ESV</Q>
        <T>
            <item>Scripture Memory</item>
        </T>
        <P>And by this we know that we have come to know him, if we keep his commandments. Whoever says “I know him” but does not keep his commandments is a liar, and the truth is not in him, but whoever keeps his word, in him truly the love of God is perfected. By this we may know that we are in him: whoever says he abides in him ought to walk in the same way in which he walked.</P>
    </passage>
</verses>