<verses name="Roman Road to Salvation">
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 3:23</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>For all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 3:10</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>There is no one righteous, not even one.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 5:12</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>Therefore, just as sin entered the world through one man, and death through sin, and in this way death came to all people, because all sinned.
		</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 6:23</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>For the wages of sin is death, but the gift of God is eternal life in Christ Jesus our Lord.
		</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 5:8</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>But God demonstrates his own love for us in this: While we were still sinners, Christ died for us.
		</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 10:9-10</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>If you declare with your mouth, “Jesus is Lord,” and believe in your heart that God raised him from the dead, you will be saved. For it is with your heart that you believe and are justified, and it is with your mouth that you profess your faith and are saved.
		</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 10:13</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>for, “Everyone who calls on the name of the Lord will be saved.”</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 8:38-39</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>For I am convinced that neither death nor life, neither angels nor demons neither the present nor the future, nor any powers, neither height nor depth, nor anything else in all creation, will be able to separate us from the love of God that is in Christ Jesus our Lord.
		</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 10:17</R>
		<Q>NIV</Q>
		<T>
			<item>Roman Road</item>
		</T>
		<P>Consequently, faith comes from hearing the message, and the message is heard through the word about Christ.
		</P>
	</passage>
</verses>