<verses name="Share The Gospel" >
	<passage>
		<R>Psalm 96:3</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>Tell of His glory among the nations, His wonderful deeds among all the peoples.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>1 Corinthians 1:17</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>For Christ did not send me to baptize, but to preach the gospel, not in cleverness of speech, so that the cross of Christ would not be made void.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>1 Chronicles 16:8</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>Oh give thanks to the Lord, call upon His name; make known His deeds among the peoples.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Romans 1:16</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>For I am not ashamed of the gospel, for it is the power of God for salvation to everyone who believes, to the Jew first and also to the Greek.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>1 Corinthians 9:16</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>For if I preach the gospel, I have nothing to boast of, for I am under compulsion; for woe is me if I do not preach the gospel.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Ephesians 6:19</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>And pray on my behalf, that utterance may be given to me in the opening of my mouth, to make known with boldness the mystery of the gospel,</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>2 Timothy 1:8</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>Therefore do not be ashamed of the testimony of our Lord or of me His prisoner, but join with me in suffering for the gospel according to the power of God</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Matthew 24:14</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>This gospel of the kingdom shall be preached in the whole world as a testimony to all the nations, and then the end will come.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Mark 8:35</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>For whoever wishes to save his life will lose it, but whoever loses his life for My sake and the gospel’s will save it.</P>
	</passage>
	<passage>
		<R>Mark 13:10</R>
		<Q>NASB</Q>
		<T><item>Share the Gospel</item></T>
		<P>The gospel must first be preached to all the nations.</P>
	</passage>
</verses>